If you've had your eye on Celo, Texas,
and are curious what affordable luxury
living really looks like here, then
stick with me today as we tour a brand
new construction home priced at
$585,000.
This home is in a very new community.
Um, it sits on a oversized halfacre
corner lot, 2600 square ft with a
mother-in-law suite. It's really
beautiful and I can't wait to show you.
[Music]
Hey, and welcome back to Living in
Central Texas. I help people from all
over the place relocate to the central
Texas area. So, if you're new to my
channel, don't forget to like,
subscribe, and click the bell
notification so that you can stay
uptodate on all things real estate here
in Central Texas. Welcome to this
fantastic new construction home in Flint
Ridge Estates in the beautiful Celo,
Texas, where smalltown charm meets
luxury new construction. This brand new
home sits on just over half an acre and
is priced at $585,000.
I love its sleek stucco and stone
exterior, spacious layout, and modern
details throughout. This 2600 square
foot home is thoughtfully designed for
refined Texas living. Step inside to
soaring vated ceilings, custom beams,
and a striking wood burning fireplace
that anchors the main living space.
Natural light fills the home,
highlighting the elegant finishes from
top to bottom.
I love the finishes in this home. The
light fixtures are absolutely beautiful,
as well as the details in the wall
accents.
The chef's kitchen features a center
island, so many cabinets, beautiful
custom cabinetry, a built-in oven,
cooktop, pot filler, and stylish vent
hood. And all open to the living and
dining area, making it ideal for
entertaining.
This home features four bedrooms and
three full bathrooms.
Including a private primary suite with a
garden tub, dual vanities, a walk-in
closet, and a separate glass shower.
There's even a dedicated home office,
perfect for working remotely or managing
your next big project.
Outback, enjoy a covered patio complete
with an outdoor kitchen and plenty of
room to breathe. The lot is already set
up for a future 30x 24 shop with a
sprinkler system and aerobic septic
system already in place.
Celledo is known for its charming
boutiques, art galleries, local
wineries, and serene creekside trails.
It's a destination town with toprated
schools, a rich history, and a relaxed
pace of life. Don't forget Mil Creek
Golf Course. Um, this community is
wildly known for its awesome golf course
living.
This home is fully complete, ready to go
with a 1.57 tax rate and low HOA fees.
This custom home is your opportunity to
enjoy upscale living in one of central
Texas's most desirable towns. If you're
thinking about moving here, be sure to
download the free relocation guide
below. It's packed with neighborhood
statistics, videos, and local insights.
Okay, friends, that wraps up our tour of
this spectacular luxury new construction
home here in Cedo, Texas. I'm so curious
what you thought. Did you love certain
elements, not love certain things? Let
me know in the comments below. I
personally love this builder. I have
been following him for years. Really
love showing his homes. There's just
certain things that I can always expect
from him. He's a he builds on a smaller
production. And so since he's not a huge
production builder, I feel like that
gives him an opportunity to really do
attention to detail, really unique
design elements. I always expect really
um grand kitchens, very functional but
beautiful. I think he places a lot of
emphasis on the kitchen and living space
being the heart of the home. His outdoor
spaces are always really great, too. I
noticed for a while there when the
market was busier, even when a lot of
builders were not doing outdoor
kitchens, he was he was doing outdoor
kitchens. He was implementing his stone
accents. And I think those little things
really go a long way. Um, if you would
like any more information on this
builder, this community, Cedo, or any
other area in Central Texas, you can
find all my contact information below.
You can also head on over to
livinginctx.com
where there are some really great
resources to moving to the area. Till
next time, I'm Andrea Dudik, realtor and
associate broker.
[Music]